Home
About Us
The Journey of Advitya
From CEOÆs Desk
From DirectorsÆ Desk
Vision & Mission
Our Team
This page shows the Team Members of Advitya Healthcares along with their designation and credentials
PancreaCare
Clinical Services
Research
Upcoming International Collaborations
Locations
Home û Kolkata
Home û Ranchi
Testimonials
Careers
Gallery
FAQs
Pancreas
GallBladder
Liver
Large Intestine
Stomach
Esophagus
Blogs
Contact Us
ERP Login
<!--

.prisna-gwt-align-left {
	text-align: left !important;
}
.prisna-gwt-align-right {
	text-align: right !important;
}



body {
	top: 0 !important;
}
.goog-te-banner-frame {
	display: none !important;
	visibility: hidden !important;
}

#goog-gt-tt,
.goog-tooltip,
.goog-tooltip:hover {
	display: none !important;
}
.goog-text-highlight {
	background-color: transparent !important;
	border: none !important;
	box-shadow: none !important;
}
.translated-rtl font,
.translated-ltr font {
	background-color: transparent !important;
	box-shadow: none !important;
	box-sizing: border-box !important;
	-webkit-box-sizing: border-box !important;
	-moz-box-sizing: border-box !important;
}

-->
/*<![CDATA[*/
function initializeGoogleTranslateElement() {
	new google.translate.TranslateElement({
		pageLanguage: "en",
		layout: google.translate.TranslateElement.InlineLayout.SIMPLE,
		includedLanguages: "bn,gu,hi,kn,ml,mr,or,ta,te"
	}, "google_translate_element");
}
/*]]&gt;*/
From Inception to Realization
ùThis is Our Journey
We were not born in a boardroom or conceived in an investorÆs plan. We were moulded in hospital corridors, in the waiting rooms of overcrowded clinics, amidst the anxious whispers of families who had travelled miles, desperate for care.
Connect with Us
2003-2008
The First Glimpse into Healthcare
We witnessed their silent prayers and unspoken fears. We saw the exhaustion in their eyes, not just from long journeys, but from the despair of realising that the care they needed was missing in their homes.
Big cities boasted world-class hospitals, yet outside them, accessáto specialised healthcare was severely limited. We witnessed families leaving their homes, their livelihoods, everything they cherished, just to grasp a few more moments with theirálovedáones. It was during those times that we realised something profoundùtreatment and healing are not the same.áMedicine should not be restricted by geography. Healthcare should not be a privilege.
2009-2015
Learning the Language of Surgery and Cancer Care
As we grew, we found ourselves in the realm of surgery and oncology. Surgery was not merely about technical skill; it was about responsibility, about standing at the threshold between despair and hope. It is a place where a few minutes and a single decision can alter the course of a life. We learned from mentors who showed us that surgery is not merely an act, but a commitmentùto ethics, to morality, and to the individuals who place their trust in our hands. We witnessed how cancer patients suffered and how their loved ones did everything possible to spend another day with them. With every lesson, we understood our purpose more clearly: expertise should not be confined to a few institutions, it should be accessible where people need it most.
2015-2023
Recognizing the Gaps, Preparing for Change
As we delved deeper, our understanding of healthcare inequities became more acute. We observed that the highest level of surgical and cancer expertise was concentrated in only a handful of institutions, while extensive areas continued to be underserved. Patients from smaller towns faced an impossible dilemma: travel to a distant city for specialised care, often too late, or settle for what was available, even if it wasnÆt sufficient.
We met families who delayed life-saving surgeries and cancer care, not because they didnÆt desire treatment but because they couldnÆt afford the weeks of travel, accommodation, and lost wages. We witnessed people making devastating sacrificesùselling land, exhausting their savingsùto reach hospitals with the needed expertise, and sometimes, even when they arrived, it was too late.
We realised then that this wasnÆt merely a logistical challenge but a fundamental flaw in healthcare delivery. Why should world-class treatment be limited to a select few hospitals? Why should a personÆs survival depend on their ability to travel? We were no longer merely observing a problem but getting ready to be the solution.
2023-2025
The Birth of Advitya
By 2023, we were no longer merely a thought. We had become a mission, a movement, a force taking shape.
We were named Advitya (meaning unique) to reflect our character and purpose. To ensure our perpetual existence, we were formally incorporated on February 21, 2025. However, you will realise that we have been around for a long time, and when you meet us, you will feel that you have missed us all along. We were born from a simple yet powerful belief: If patients cannot access the finest surgical and cancer care, the finest care should be brought to them.
We have re-imagined our approach. Instead of merely being just another large hospital in a metropolitan area, we chose a different route: collaborating with hospitals in second- and third-tier cities, equipping them with expertise, technology, and training to provide world-class gastrointestinal, hepatopancreatobiliary surgical care, and cancer care.
This Alliance Model goes beyond merely expanding services. It focuses on keeping families together when they need one another the most. It aims at strengthening hospitals, empowering local doctors, and ensuring that people donÆt just receive treatment but genuinely healùphysically, emotionally, and financially.
We are evolving. With each partnership, every successful surgery, and every patient who no longer has to leave their home for the best care, our purpose becomes ever stronger.
We were born from a problem, yet we exist to provide a solution.
Today and Beyond, we, Advitya, bring you Science for Humanity. Thisà is merely the Beginning.
Stay Updated with Advitya
Subscribe to our newsletter for the latest updates, news, events, and healthcare insights from Advitya Healthcares.
Science for Humanity
Contact Details:
+91 9211221551 / 9211221552
+91 9211221553 / 9211221554
info@advityahealthcares.com
Website Updated as of March 3, 2026
Home
About Us
Blog
Careers
Clinical Services
FAQs
Research
Contact Us
PancreaCare
MA Pest Control LLP
Glopal Management and Services
Employee Email
Registered Office:
603, Tower C, 6th Floor, Nirvana Courtyard, Sector 50, Gurugram 122018
⌐ 2025 Advitya Healthcares. All rights reserved.
WhatsApp Us
